Guide to the Diane Middlebrook, English 258, Tutored Video Instruction, Videorecordings SC1294
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Diane Middlebrook, English 258, Tutored Video Instruction, Videorecordings
1977
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Middlebrook, Diane Wood
SC1294
2.5 Linear Feet (19 videotapes in 5 boxes)
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of 19 videotapes used as instruction tools in Dianne Middlebrook's course English 258: Twentieth-Century Neo-Romantic British and American Poetry.
Distance education -- Computer-assisted instruction; Middlebrook, Diane Wood
- Diane Middlebrook T.S. Eliot "Little Gidding", 1977-01-24; 1.1; 1 videocassette(s) (Box 1)
- Diane Middlebrook "Intimations" part 1, 1977-01-10; 1.2; 1 videocassette(s) (Box 1)
- Diane Middlebrook "Intimations" part 2, 1977-01-12; 1.3; 1 videocassette(s) (Box 1)
- Diane Middlebrook T.S. Eliot - Burnt Norton, 1977-01-19; 1.4 (Box 1)
- Diane Middlebrook Hart Crane, part 3, 1977-02-02; 2.1; 1 videocassette(s) (Box 2)
- Diane Middlebrook Hart Crane, part 2, 1977-02-01; 2.2; 1 videocassette(s) (Box 2)
- Diane Middlebrook Hart Crane, part 1, 1977-01-31; 2.3; 1 videocassette(s) (Box 2)
- Diane Middlebrook Dylan Thomas, 1977-01-25; 2.4; 1 videocassette(s) (Box 2)
- Diane Middlebrook Wallace Stevens "Last Poems", 1977-02-18; 3.1; 1 videocassette(s) (Box 3)
- Diane Middlebrook Wallace Stevens "Toward a Supreme fiction," part 1, 1977-02-18; 3.2; 1 videocassette(s) (Box 3)
- Diane Middlebrook Wallace Stevens, 1977-02-17; 3.3; 1 videocassette(s) (Box 3)
- Diane Middlebrook Wallace Stevens "Toward a Supreme fiction," part 2, 1977-02-16; 3.4; 1 videocassette(s) (Box 3)
- Diane Middlebrook Theodore Roethre #3, 1977-03-02; 4.1; 1 videocassette(s) (Box 4)
- Diane Middlebrook Theodore Roethre #2 "The Loss Sum", 4.2; 1 videocassette(s) (Box 4)
- Diane Middlebrook Theodore Roethre #1 "The Premonition", 1977-02-25; 4.3; 1 videocassette(s) (Box 4)
- Diane Middlebrook Wallace Stevens "The Rock", 1977-02-23; 4.4; 1 videocassette(s) (Box 4)
- Diane Middlebrook Theodore Roethre #4 "North American", 1977-03-04; 5.1; 1 videocassette(s) (Box 5)
- Diane Middlebrook Theodore Roethre #5 "The Far Field", 1977-03-07; 5.2; 1 videocassette(s) (Box 5)
- Diane Middlebrook Theodore Roethre #6 "The Far Field", 1977-03-08; 5.3; 1 videocassette(s) (Box 5)